Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
Come on, sir, give us a penny!
Run!
Sorry.
Lucky heather, sir?
Come on, sir.
Looking for someone?
Er... Yes, actually, I...
Mr. Gray.
Welcome to London, sir.
Go on, lady. Off you go!
Whoa.
And here we are, sir.
Welcome home.
I hope you'll find everything
to your liking, sir.
Nothing's changed since I was a boy.
Sir.
I'm sorry for your loss, sir.
May I prepare some tea?
Thank you, Victor.
I've no doubt London will hold many
new friends and adventures for you.
- I hope so.
- So do I.
Oh! This is somebody
you simply must meet.
This is one of our finest artists,
Basil Hallward.
Agatha, please,
a humble student of beauty.
- Oh.
- What do you think?
That's quite a likeness.
- Basil.
- Hmm?
I've been in London two weeks now.
And the only people I've met
are Agatha's charitable group.
Well, you've met me.
Of course.
I didn't mean...
These parties are terribly dull, Dorian.
- You won't be missing anything.
- I'm sure you're right.
I just...
...thought it might be fun.
Dear me, no.
Shabby.
Wife, drink.
There. I'll fetch us some drinks.
Find her a good husband
who knows how to behave to a woman.
The only way to behave is
to make love to her if she's pretty
and to someone else if she's plain.
Excuse me.
Cigarette?
No, thank you.
I find a cigarette to be
the perfect pleasure.
It is exquisite...
...and leaves one unsatisfied.
You're Kelso's grandson.
Yes.
- Did you know him?
- I met him once.
It was enough
to give a cheer last month
when he rasped his last sour breath.
One assumes you inherited
the withered old goat's estate?
Being a little orphan isn't all bad.
"An earnest young man with a beautiful
nature," according to Agatha.
I'd pictured some freckled country oaf
in ghastly dress.
I see I was only half right.
It could be worse.
Gladys Allonby's been dressed for her
14th birthday ever since her 40th.
If Radley spent less time in church
and more at his tailor's,
he might not so resemble
a badly-bound hymn book.
Are you sure you won't take a cigarette?
I get them directly from Cairo.
I see you've met our charming host.
Hm?
Just pay no attention
to anything he tells you.
How rude. Henry Wotton.
Victoria, my wife.
My aunt, alas, you know.
Oh, I'm so glad you've met.
You might learn some manners from this boy.
I've found some more guests
for you to insult.
I knew I kept her for something.
I do hope our paths cross again, Mr. Gray.
Thank you for the cigarette...
cigarette.
An acquired taste.
- No, it's actually quite pleasant.
- No, I meant Henry.
There's some people I want you to meet.
Dorian...
Aren't you tired of
looking at me yet?
Certainly not.
The more I look...
...the more I see.
It must be nearly finished, man.
It isn't the Sistine Chapel.
Do you remember when I told you
you could sit in if you were quiet?
- I want to see it.
- No, no, don't.
He won't even let me have a peek.
Agatha tells me your father
was also an artist.
- Apparently so.
- Kelso must have been delighted,
his daughter falling
for some penniless painter.
No wonder they eloped.
- Well, I never knew my parents.
- Of course.
Typhus is so awful.
Your poor mother carried off in childbirth.
Do you take such interest
in everyone you meet?
Not everyone I meet is so interesting.
Henry, why don't you go for a stroll,
while I just work up the background?
You don't need Dorian for that.
Let's both take a break.
- Perhaps we should all get some air.
- Yes, and I know just the place.
Look. It's rancid! It's rancid!
It's only five days old. I'm not paying.
Come on, Dorian.
Sorry.
You see why Agatha is so keen
to help Whitechapel?
Don't you think we should at least try
to make a difference?
I've no desire to change anything
in England, except the weather.
Welcome to my little Hellfire Club.
- Here you are, gents.
- In one.
No, don't, don't.
Barkeeper.
Again.
How say you and the handsome
young man stuff me double?
Er, no, thank you.
We nonetheless wish you godspeed
on your evening's quest for romance.
A little wider, my dear.
Don't worry. He's a doctor.
There's no shame in pleasure, Mr. Gray.
You see, man just wants to be happy.
But society wants him to be good.
And when he's good, Man is rarely happy.
But when he's happy, he's always good.
You do want to be good,
don't you, Mr. Gray, and happy?
Isn't there a price to pay
for that sort of business?
She's quite affordable.
But what I was asking
was about the effect on...
Buy a lady a drink?
- On what?
- Well, on one's soul.
One's soul?
This is my church.
With this dram, right now,
I nail my soul to the Devil's altar.
You'll never meet a more eloquent
philosopher of pure folly.
Come on, Dorian.
It's time we showed you what we've made.
- Really?
- The boy hasn't finished his gin.
Go and fiddle with your background.
We'll be along shortly.
Your picture awaits you, Dorian.
Perhaps you should go and speak to her.
I didn't realize she...
Don't be timid. Go.
- I wouldn't know where to...
- You see, I envy you.
Me?
Everything's possible for you
because you have
the only two things worth having.
Youth...
and beauty.
Come on, let's go.
The moment's lost.
That was probably her husband.
Yes, very sensible.
People die of common sense, Dorian,
one lost moment at a time.
Life is a moment.
There is no hereafter.
So make it burn always
with the hardest flame.
Well, Basil...
...it's quite the best thing
you've done.
You'll be the talk of the town.
Both of you.
Speak up, boy.
You'll hurt his feelings.
Is that really how I look?
It's just so...
...life-like.
Better than life.
He'll always look like that.
You, Mr. Gray, I'm afraid will not.
In time, Mother Nature will come
a very poor second to Father Basil.
- Some things are precious for not lasting.
- Poppycock.
We wither and scar
because the gods are cruel and hateful.
Perhaps I should nail my soul
to the Devil's altar.
And remain as you are?
Fair trade.
How about another gin instead?
All that hocus-pocus, endless conjurations,
books bound in infant skin,
pentacles of fire,
drinking the blood of virgins.
Dorian wouldn't really barter his soul.
Would you, Dorian?
Would you?
Yes.
Oh, you really have captured
something quite exquisite, Basil.
I've never known a subject so unaffected.
The brush just seemed to dance
and I just painted what I saw.
Kelso will turn in his grave.
He didn't care to look at me.
He blamed me for my mother,
for her death.
There are no limits
to the ugliness of old men.
Lips!
- And his eyes!
Almost a match for the original.
I'm afraid you're gonna have to
get used to being looked at.
Well, it's a fine painting.
- I don't mean the painting.
- Mr. Gray, if you please.
That went rather well, didn't it?
- A triumph, Mr. Gray.
The first of many.
May I say, sir,
your mother would be very proud
to see you today.
Shall I draw your bath?
It's rather early.
Do we have any gin?
I believe not, sir.
Then perhaps you might
summon me a hansom?
- Go on, poke him!
- I am poking him!
Check his pockets!
Yes?
- Wet your pizzle, sir?
- Hello, handsome.
Boy!
Have a box, my lord?
Just a bob.
You've only missed a little.
This young lady...
Miss Sibyl Vane, my lord,
in the role of Ophelia.
...see that noble
and most sovereign reason
like sweet bells jangled,
out of tune and harsh.
That unmatched form
and feature of blown youth
blasted with ecstasy.
Oh, woe is me.
May I present
the Theatre Royale's
Miss Sibyl Vane, my lord?
I'm not really a lord.
I don't know why he keeps saying that.
We don't get many gentlemen
in this theatre.
Really?
Well, then, I shall recommend it...
...to them.
May I ask what brings you
to my dressing room?
Well, I...
I just happened
to be passing the theatre and...
- Well, you see, I was in the gin shop...
- I know.
You remember?
Well, a friend took me there
for the first time.
Well, I say the first time.
Of course, I have...
Well, I wanted to...
wanted to say hello, but...
...then you left with...
- With Jim.
- Yes.
Quite.
Jim.
My brother.
Brother?
- Mm.
- Well, that's splendid!
Sorry. It was wrong of me to...
Please forgive my intrusion,
Miss Vane.
Wait! There's something
you haven't told me.
Yes, of course.
I do beg your pardon.
Ophelia is a most challenging role
and your performance this evening
was... impeccable.
In fact, extraordinary.
In fact...
...you are extraordinary.
And when I saw you on the stage,
and even more so,
now I stand before you,
I am awestruck and humbled
by your radiance.
I meant your name.
You didn't tell me your name.
So, how many other girls
do you bring here?
Hundreds.
Thousands.
- You must be courting dozens at least.
- No.
You can tell me the truth.
There's only you.
Tell me, what are your actual relations
with this young thing?
- A fraction of respect, man.
- It's not like that. Sibyl's sacred.
It's only the scared things
that are worth touching.
People nowadays fear their passions.
- Well, I don't.
- Of course you do.
We're taught terror from the nursery.
Terror of God,
or, even worse, of scandal.
We're taught to spend our entire lives
cowering in self-denial.
The truth, Mr. Gray, is that every
impulse we strangle only poisons us.
You'll make him wish
he'd never mentioned the girl.
Voila, monsieur.
There's something missing.
Thank you, Harry.
I took the liberty of filling
it with my blend.
Oh, Dorian.
It's beautiful.
I just thought it would suit you.
I should be going.
Jim will worry.
Of course.
Or we could...
I mean...
You could...
...stay...
...here...
...with me.
We shouldn't be afraid of our feelings, Sib.
It's just...
I've seen other girls
who give themselves, and then
I've seen what becomes of them.
I love you.
Forgive me. I didn't mean...
You're all I ever want in the world.
Boy!
You might have a little scar there.
Well, it won't be a first.
My back.
What?
You're perfect.
- Engaged?
- It's wonderful, isn't it?
I wanted you all
to be the first to know.
- Congratulations, Dorian.
- Thank you.
May I ask how you came
to propose marriage?
I suppose I didn't really make
a formal proposal.
I told her I loved her. She said it was
her dream come true to be my wife.
Women are wonderfully practical.
Will you all come
and see her perform tonight?
I'm afraid I have an engagement.
And we're due at the Burdons.
Tell Burdon I'll see him tomorrow.
Why don't you hail us a hansom, Dorian?
- I love acting.
- Goodbye, ladies.
So much more real than life.
I hope you're pleased with yourself.
Every experience is of value.
And marriage is certainly an experience.
Nobody is amused this time, Henry.
I'll talk to him.
I got the sense the others
don't quite approve.
Especially Basil.
Perhaps Basil should be a little more
fearless with his own feelings.
I thought we might make a little stop
en route to the theatre.
I too have news.
It seems my wife is with child.
Oh, congratulations.
Don't be absurd.
It's the beginning of the end.
So, indulge me.
- Ah, Harry.
- Alan.
Firkytoodling at last, I see.
- Come along, ladies.
- It's good to see you.
How delightful.
Hello.
Drink up.
It won't be long before
you're anchored to the perambulator.
I don't think so.
Our friend is to marry.
Ah, but we haven't had a chance
to win your heart.
Oh, well.
Farewell to youth.
No.
Watch your step.
Does Victoria know you come here?
My dear boy, the one of marriage is that...
...it makes a life of deception
absolutely necessary.
Well, perhaps I have
a stronger conscience.
Conscience is just
a polite term for cowardice.
No civilized man regrets a pleasure.
You see?
The only way to get rid of a temptation
is to yield to it.
Be searching always
for new sensations, Dorian.
Come.
Come upstairs.
Forbid yourself nothing.
- Come.
- Nobody at all need know.
Come with me.
The pleasure is all mine.
- I've heard so much about you.
- And I you.
Did you enjoy the show?
I couldn't see you in the audience.
I'm afraid we ran a little late.
Oh, where were you?
At the club.
The truth is, my dear,
we were celebrating your wonderful news.
Very many congratulations.
And Harry is to be a father.
How wonderful.
- Indeed.
- In one.
I'm sure you're eager to
start a family yourself?
Very much.
Well, not quite yet.
- Good night.
- Good night, Charlie.
Good night.
We're a little young, don't you think?
Are we?
Perhaps I should take my leave.
- Good night.
- Er...
See you tomorrow, Harry.
I'm sure.
I don't think we need to rush, that's all.
You sound different.
Not at all.
Were you at the club all night?
Yes.
He's a better liar than you.
What?
I was just saying everything is so soon.
- I gave myself to you.
- Sibyl, please!
- I thought you loved me.
- And I do!
Then make me your wife,
not one of your whores!
I think perhaps I ought to go.
Don't let him do this, Dorian.
- This has nothing to do with Harry.
- You said you loved me!
And I do! I do!
Dorian, please!
Please, Dorian!
Please, I love you!
Oh, Henry! Dorian!
Tell me, how was last night's performance?
I'm sorry.
Have a drink.
I can introduce you to the
artist later, if you like.
Never marry, Mr. Gray.
It's the only way to keep
all one's illusions.
Chin up, dear boy.
You've a face like a slapped nancy.
You'll love again.
And again.
Do you have your cigarettes?
Of course.
Don't fear it, Dorian.
The world is yours.
For a season.
Hello, Victor.
Could you fetch us a bottle of the...?
Anything!
- What's the matter?
- You've a visitor, sir.
A Mr. Vane.
He seems disturbed.
We'll wait in the library.
Victor, how about that bottle?
To what do I owe the pleasure, Jim?
Can I er...
Can I get you something to drink?
I don't want this in my house.
What happened with Sibyl
was very unfortunate.
But this was a gift
and she really should keep...
It's filthy.
She was wearing it
when they pulled her from the river.
Why on earth was she...?
She... she can't...
She can't...
I wanted you to know... she loved you.
She was going to have your child.
And you killed her.
Jim! Jim!
Get up!
Are you all right, sir?
Let me... Let me...
...help you up.
- Sibyl's dead.
- Come.
- Now, now.
- Good night, ladies.
Get up. Get up!
We can't have maniacs threatening
decent people in their own homes.
Alan treats a number of
such deranged cases at Broadmoor.
Just until he settles down.
I feel confident that any inquest
into this unfortunate business
will find no connection
whatsoever with Mr. Gray.
Taking you downtown.
This wasn't your fault, Dorian.
- Kelso said I was death.
- Well, he was wrong.
Salome.
- Harry!
- And...
You're not making sense.
No! Please!
He's part of me, Harry.
- I turn all love into death.
- Dorian. Dorian!
Into death. Death!
Kelso was a bitter ruin of a man
and he's dead.
What's past is past.
Experience makes us strong, Dorian.
And you need to see this episode
for what it really is.
An extraordinary experience.
- I can't be so heartless.
- It isn't heartless.
It's finding a perspective.
Most lack the strength
to rise above life's suffering.
To rule one's emotions,
to savor them...
...that takes a man of will.
Alan left this for you.
Drink. Doctor's orders.
I should be going.
I'll call in the morning.
Thank you, Harry.
You are a man of will, Dorian.
I knew it from the first.
Dorian, Dorian...
I'm so, so sorry.
Harry... Harry told me
about poor Sibyl.
If there's anything I can do...
anything...
You're very kind. I'm actually
just on my way to see Harry now.
- Are you coming to the Radleys' ball?
- Er...
Where's my picture?
The light was too strong in here.
The light was perfect.
Where have you put it?
It's quite safe.
The truth is,
I don't want it on public show.
It's just too valuable.
I could forgive the vagaries of grief
if you actually seemed to be grieving.
I was...
stricken.
But what's past is past.
Every experience is of value.
Drink?
You shouldn't believe
every word Harry says.
He doesn't.
Isn't this all just ghastly?
Radley gloating with pitiful pride
...while his love-starved wife
parades their daughter
...like a sow truffling for husbands.
Delightful little filly.
And poor Celia.
Trussed up in a doily for some
chinless miscreant to eternally enslave.
I suggest we raise a little hell.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I know who you are, Mr. Gray.
Allow me to offer my congratulations
on your ravishing debut.
Perhaps a small toast.
To what?
Intoxication.
- Here she comes.
- Who?
Celia?
- Celia?
- Problem, Lady Radley?
My daughter, I can't find her.
And nor can I find your Mr. Gray.
Perhaps they're in the garden.
The arrangements are marvelous.
Might I hazard
an alternative suggestion?
Celia!
- Is something the matter?
- Celia!
Where is my daughter, you beast?
I was just attending to my costume.
A little of Lord Radley's very fine
Burgundy was spilt on my shirt cuff.
Mr. Gray, I...
- Lord Henry gave me to understand...
- A mistake.
Nobody at all need know.
You're too kind, Mr. Gray.
- Thank you.
- It must be difficult,
a party like this.
Seeing your daughter come of age.
Makes you long for your own youth.
I...
Madam, forgive me but...
...you are exquisite.
Oh, Mr. Gray.
This is most improper.
Now, where were we?
What are you grinning about, Gray?
I think Harry's just lost a wager.
Well, come on, out with it.
We're all gambling men here.
Just a little round of double or nothing.
Of course, a good gambler
understands that there are limits.
There are no limits.
Have a wonderful birthday, Dorian!
Dorian.
This crush is your finest yet.
One has to do something
to null the pain of age.
Do tell my husband
not to be so disagreeable.
But I always agree with him.
Congratulations, Basil.
I hear you have a new exhibition.
Yes, yes, in Paris.
Yes, in fact, I wanted
to ask a question of you, Dorian.
I'd like to make your portrait
my principal piece.
Oh, yes, that picture.
Absolutely wonderful.
- Whatever became of it?
- I haven't seen it myself in some months.
- Dorian's very protective of it, aren't you?
- Indeed I am.
I'm very sorry, Basil,
but it's just too precious.
I won't have it out of the house.
I beg your pardon.
Did you want me?
That picture is my finest work
and it'd be greatly appreciated...
The greatest gift that anyone
could ever have given.
In fact...
In fact, I wish that
I could tell you just how great.
But then it isn't so unreasonable
to borrow it back a little while.
I'm not sure that I've ever...
...fully expressed my gratitude.
I hardly think...
I have the key to your heart.
Don't touch that ever!
Dorian!
He's young.
But he was never cruel...
...till he met you.
That's mine.
Oh, it's you.
- I thought you'd gone home.
- I just needed a walk.
I was just about to go to bed.
Everyone's left.
I'm here to see you, not them.
Really?
Wait, wait.
I don't know where to begin.
How ominous.
- You terrified that poor boy tonight.
- He seemed to recover.
Is that what you tell yourself
about Celia Radley?
Look, I'm sorry about her misfortune.
But do you really believe
that I'm to blame?But I know you're treating people poorly.
Even me,
when I ask you the small favor
that you loan me my own picture...
- Is that what this is about?
- No, it's about a good damn more!
Dorian...
What happened
to the Dorian Gray I painted?
You just don't understand.
I will always...
...be that Dorian.
Can I trust you, Basil?
Would you like to see
why you can never exhibit that picture?
What's the matter?
Don't you recognize me?
What? What have you...?
That thing...
It isn't what...
Together, we've created
something beautiful.
It's a miracle.
Look at me.
Because of your painting...
- It's not...
- this will never age.
Will never scar.
Can you even imagine...
being able to do anything you please...
...and live out every whim and impulse
while the world just sees you gleam?
This isn't you.
I know this isn't you.
We can stop it!
Basil, please, don't.
Don't you see
that this must be destroyed?
Dorian, I want to help you.
We'll find a priest or a spirit-worker.
There's good in your heart.
I've seen it.
You're not this...
...this devil!
I'm a god.
Basil.
Basil!
Good evening.
Need some help, sir?
How kind.
Alright.
Mind how you go, sir.
On you go.
Good day, Lady Victoria.
I was about to take Harry
for lunch at Scott's.
Why don't you join us?
Oh, Dorian. You haven't heard.
They've found Basil's body in the river.
Thou art slave to Fate,
Chance, kings and desperate men,
And dost with poison, warre
and sickness dwell,
Poppies or charmes
can make us sleep as well,
And better than thy stroke.
Why swell'st thou then?
One short sleep past,
we wake eternally.
And death shall be no more.
Death, thou shalt die.
Farewell, dear Basil.
I spoke to the police again this morning.
And have the buffoons managed
to make a single inch of progress?
They're convinced it was
some Shadwell renter.
They think they'll catch him.
So Basil's name
will be dragged through the gutter.
I'm of a mind to take a trip, Harry.
Maybe you should join me.
- Where are you going?
- Everywhere.
I leave tomorrow.
With all this?
Someone once gave me
some fine advice...
...about taking perspective.
Come with me.
The child is imminent.
Tell me everything.
I always do.
I've entered the tombs of dead nations,
ridden with our last savage tribes.
I feel the brilliance of every moment,
the splendor of existence and its awful...
...keen as the edge of a blade,
this desperate will to see, touch and...
Dearest Harry, you taught me
that life must burn with a hard flame.
Its light does not blind me,
...nor its heat sear me.
I am the flame, Harry.
I am the flame.
Women never have anything to say,
but they say it charmingly.
They're the great triumph
of matter over mind.
Well, here I am.
Dorian.
You look so...
...so...
He looks magnificent.
We have heard such tales.
I'm afraid they're all absolutely
and entirely... true.
Welcome back.
Some champagne?
Yes.
A- ha!
My missing guest of honor.
I'm coming.
I was sorry for your loss.
You know, I kept hearing this phrase.
"Natural causes. "
Nature has a great deal to answer for.
She was so looking forward
to the life of a divorcee.
And poor old Basil...
If we paid the police by results,
we'd save the Treasury thousands.
When your letters stopped coming,
I feared the worst.
But here you are.
So never mind the country estate.
Tell me, why are you really back?
- I'm tired.
- You don't look it.
You have no right to melancholy.
Your life is exquisite.
You've drunk deeply of everything
and it hasn't left a fleck on you.
Do you remember
when I first came to London?
I felt so...
Those were the great days.
Dorian, it's quite clear
why you've lost your passion for life.
You've been away from me for too long.
We must go out.
Take on the town, as we used to.
- I've missed you, Harry.
- I must ask you, though...
What is your secret?
If I told you, I'd have to kill you.
You still have it, I see.
- From Cairo.
- Where else?
Smile.
Emily.
May I?
I hope I'm not interrupting
your reminiscence?
The one charm of the past
is that it's the past.
Oh. I hope you're not also
a dreary old cynic?
What is there to believe in?
Our developments.
All I see is decay.
Well, then religion?
Fashionable substitute for belief.
- Art?
- A malady.
- Love?
- An illusion.
Bravo!
Well, you both cut the world to pieces,
don't you?
Thank you for the cigarette.
Unusual woman.
She ought to be.
She's my daughter.
Lie down.
Dorian?
Dorian...
It's you.
Dorian!
Oi, mister!
Give us a penny!
Oi, mister. Mister.
Penny for the guy?
- Have you been in the war?
- I'm too old.
Give us a couple of bob
for a drink, will you?
Get up. Get up!
You...
Yeah, you... Dorian Gray.
- I think you're mistaken.
- I knew one day you'd come back.
- Wait, please...
- So many years I've waited.
Wait! How many years?
- No more!
- How many years?
Look at me.
Look at my face.
I'm barely 20, man.
Can't be.
I don't know this...
...this Dorian Gray.
I think, sir, you are not well.
I...
Hospital.
They hurt me.
You tell him...
You tell him I'm coming.
A visitor, sir.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I thought you might like
to join me for lunch.
No, I don't think...
I made a picnic.
Yes, well, I'm afraid I...
I'd rather stay at home today.
Serious?
It's going to rain.
Tell me, Mr. Gray.
Must you always play the cynic?
Hm?
Look up.
Actually, I'd rather you didn't...
Oblige me, Mr. Gray.
Have you been pursuing
this delightful hobby for long?
No. It's a gift from my father.
In return, he made me promise that I
wouldn't chain myself to anymore railings.
For suffrage, Mr. Gray.
Well, don't you think that
women should be given the vote?
I believe a woman should be given anything
she can't wear in the evening.
What a loss to the Front you are.
Think of all those Germans that
you could bayonet with your epigrams.
I do apologize if I offend.
Oh, no, you'll have to do
rather better to offend me.
Then I humbly vow
to redouble my efforts.
You know, I wonder if it's true,
what they say about you.
That beneath all the charm,
you're in fact quite heartless?
They say I'm charming?
They say that you devote
your whole life to pleasure.
Well, it's clearly to be recommended.
If I look as good as you in 25 years,
I shall be thoroughly happy.
I can assure you, pleasure is
very different from happiness.
I mean, some things are more precious
because they don't last.
Mr. Gray...
...I believe I know your secret.
You do have a heart.
Those who go beneath the surface
do so at their peril.
How terrifying.
I may let you
chauffeur me again, Mr. Gray.
So, I'll see you at Toynbee Hall tonight?
Until then.
Alice.
I'd crawl the sewers before
I'd let my flesh and blood near him.
- Sit down, Granddad!
- What kind of unholiness...
...grants the face of a babe
to such a man?
Come along!
Come along, my dear!
Completely unnatural!
What?
- Let him play!
- Quiet, please, ladies and gentlemen.
You know, anyone would think
you're ashamed to be seen with me.
What happened in the hall?
I don't know what you mean.
You saw something.
You're mistaken.
Well, I heard that he killed him.
We never ever again...
Mr. Gray!
It would be better
if we were not seen together.
Better for whom?
Tongues may wag against you.
I don't care what they say.
You should.
The truth is,
I've done dreadful things.
My life...
My life has been a monstrous corruption.
And there will be a price.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
We should not meet again.
I told you it was him.
Step back.
I'm coming for you, Dorian Gray.
You dirty bastard!
Dorian Gray, you bastard!
You're a disgrace!
Good evening, sir.
Mr. Harcourt here thinks
there may be rats nesting in the attic.
- I haven't the key.
- Get out of my house.
But, Mr. Gray...
And you.
With respect, sir...
...I've been with your family
for two generations.
Your effects will follow.
I want to be free.
I want to be...
new,
clean.
I want to be good.
Please.
Please, you have to help me.
If we repents,
God is faithful and just.
Confess your mortal sins.
- Confess your mortal...
- This is not my true face!
If you could see my soul...
Child, only God may see our souls.
I have seen my soul!
And I could show it to you.
It's rotten.
It stinks.
It's poison.
Help me.
You will die.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Gray?
Miss Wotton.
Please forgive my intrusion...
...at this late hour.
You're shaking.
- Look, come and sit by the fire.
- I want to...
I want to tell you...
I want to tell you everything.
All right. Look at me.
Sh! What is it?
I need you...
I need you to know...
- what I am.
- Sh!
It's all right.
Listen, sh...
Harry.
Good morning.
Sleep well?
Mr. Gray was in need of a friend.
Perhaps you could ask Mrs. Williams
to prepare me some breakfast?
Of course.
So young.
The world is hers.
- Harry, I...
- How dare you!
- She's my daughter.
- I've changed.
You've changed?
But you don't change,
do you, Dorian?
Why is that?
- Harry, you're my oldest friend...
- You're against nature.
You stay away from her.
- I don't want this to get...
- Stay away from her!
Mr. Gray!
I should apologize for my father.
Last night, you wanted to
tell me something.
- Dorian!
- I want to begin again.
Far away from everything here.
I see. Well, I wouldn't...
Everything except you.
Dorian!
Yes.
Are you sure this
is what you want?
You're what I want.
As I recall, Mr. Gray stored
it in the attic.
He certainly wanted to protect it.
What secrets does he unlock?
Nobody at all need know.
Emily!
- What's the meaning of this?
- I'm sorry...
Don't come up here.
Please.
Never.
Give me the key, please, Emily.
- Well, what's in there?
- Give me the key!
What's in there?
Please.
I beg you.
It's imperative it sails with us.
To New York.
I shall wrap it myself, but I'd be grateful
if you'd send men to help carry it down.
Thank you.
The house should fetch a
fine price, Mr. Gray.
Will you be leaving
any of the furnishings?
All of them.
You know, I think that he wants
to make amends.
We owe him the benefit of the doubt.
I couldn't let you go off to that
ghastly continent without a farewell.
Come.
I hear you sail at dawn?
How romantic.
- Oh, to be young again.
- Easily done.
Can you recall any great errors
you made in your early days?
Very many, with much clarity.
Then commit them over again.
To get back one's youth,
one merely has to repeat one's follies.
Or you could barter your soul.
Darling, are you all right?
Clumsy.
Sorry, excuse me, will you?
Sorry, darling, have you seen Harry?
No. But look.
Look what he dug out.
You never told me
there was a painting of you.
Where is it?
The war's this way, mate!
Harry.
I want to see it.
See what?
- Basil's picture.
- Basil's picture was destroyed years ago.
I never liked it.
Show me.
It's an old portrait of my grandfather.
Would you really kill me, Harry?
You taught me
that a man can rule his emotions.
But I can't.
I can't help that
I love your daughter...
...more than I've loved anything
in my entire life.
And I can't help how dear
I still hold our friendship.
Please...
Please don't do this.
Just old trinkets, Harry.
Why don't we go back to the party?
Basil...
Harry...
What are you?
I am what you made me!
I lived the life that you preached
but never dared practice.
I am everything
that you were too afraid to be.
But I was trying...
I was trying so hard...
...to be a better man.
I'm sorry.
Kelso was right.
You are... You're death.
Dorian?
Dorian!
Harry, no!
No!
No! Come with me!
- What?
What are you doing?
Where's Dorian?
Dorian?
Locked!
- Emily! No, leave him!
- No, no... No!
Dorian...
Give me the key.
Look, give me the key!
What's in there?
You have my whole heart, Emily.
Leave him!
My whole heart.
What...?
Emily, I beg you...
No...
Dorian!
No! Dorian!
I'm still her father, Agatha.
And I'm merely asking
that you tell her...
...that I miss her...
...and that this will always
be her home.
And maybe one day
she'll want to listen.
Poor boy.
Who can bear to look at you now?